Just found this note|in my mailbox.
Says you're retiring?|What the hell?
Yes, ma'am. It's true.
Now why would you want to do|something stupid like that?
My doc says|I got a bum ticker,
have to take it easy|from now on.
I'm on a plane to Waikiki.|- Well, this is very annoying.
Who's gonna fix my water heater|when it breaks?
Oh, I met this young guy|named Toby.
Very bright, just turned 30.|He'll take care of you.
I am not comfortable|with strangers in my house.
Took me ten years to trust you.|- I know.
Most of those guys leave tools|and nails all over the place.
You never leave a mess.
Thank you, ma'am.
Have you told everyone else|you're leaving?
I left copies of that same note|in everybody's mailbox.
Well, that's not right.
After all these years, people|will want to say good-bye,
and... you know, maybe throw you|a party or somethin'.
Oh, no. I prefer to go quietly,|if you know what I mean.
I don't want a big fuss.
There will never be|another one like you.
for the very last time.
No, no.
No, it can't be Friday,
because, remember, we agreed|that we would start next week?
So again, thank you so much|for this opportunity.
Subtitles by LeapinLar